qala.com.sg 2008-12-17

# QALA Singapore > Privacy Policy

Home > Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

QALA has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website: http://www.qala.com.sg 

We use your IP address to help increase efficiency, diagnose possible problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site.

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

This site contains links to other sites. QALA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our "online shop" uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers).

Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys and competitions ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor w hen necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact QALA Webmaster.
